Filming a gangster movie, are we?
Wang Guili.
I'm Inspector Chen Jiadong, West Kowloon Anti-Triad Squad.
Officer.
What's this about?
I run a legitimate business here.
Just standing here chatting with the boys.
Is that against the law now?
We suspect you're involved
in several prostitution and loan-sharking cases.
You don't have to say anything,
unless you want to.
But whatever you do say
will be written down
and used as evidence.
You're under arrest.
Do you understand?
I'll ask you once more.
Do all of you understand?
Understood.
Do you understand?
Take them in.
Yes, sir.
Against the wall, get down!
Hands behind your head.
Show me your hands.
Everybody, down!
Get down!
Behave yourself.
Come here.
Move it!
I've been on this loan shark case for a long time.
Keep up.
It's not as simple as I thought.
There's probably money laundering involved,
and overseas transactions.
But after today,
they'll lay low for a while.
Thanks for the intel.
Be careful.
Come on.
Elephant, you'll rot in hell!
You'll rot in hell!
Stop it!
Rot in hell!
Move it!
Quiet down, all of you!
Calm down!
Okay, okay, okay.
We've cracked several major criminal cases,
including a series of gang-related violence.
This includes forced prostitution,
loan sharking, and other illegal activities.
In this operation,
we've achieved a major victory.
Don't be afraid. It's all right.
We have the evidence.
They won't get away.
I used to...
hope for this day every single day,
wondering when they'd finally be caught,
when they'd finally get what's coming to them.
They forced me,
ruined me,
and wrecked my life beyond repair.
But now that this day has actually come...
Brother Qiang.
Tell me, what am I supposed to do now?
Where else am I supposed to get the money?
What have I got left to save my dad?
There was once a monster.
It was locked in a cage.
For thousands of years.
Every day, it hoped
someone would save it,
and give it back its freedom.
But when that day finally came,
the beast wanted to kill
the very person who had saved it.
As a kid, I never understood it.
But now I get it.
It's not that freedom is bad.
It's that while it was in that cage,
it had already rotted away.
The way I see it,
I am that monster.
You see,
I may seem free now,
but inside, I rotted away long ago.
Brother Qiang, you know what you just said,
"Don't be afraid,"
"It's all right,"
do you know how much I used to want to hear that?
I really, really wanted to hear it.
If only a little sooner,
there had been someone
who rushed to my side
to say those words to me,
to pull me back,
to tell me...
would everything...
It's too late.
It's too late now.
What Xie Guanhong's been up to lately,
you've all seen clearly.
He preaches loyalty and honor,
but stabs his own brothers in the back.
How can we follow a man like that?
Sooner or later, Heyisheng
is gonna be ruined by him.
No unity, no honor,
so what the hell's left to prosper?
I'll say just one thing.
Xie Guanhong is unfit to be the boss,
and unworthy of the Dragon Head Baton.
We need to find someone
who values loyalty and follows the rules,
someone who can hold down the fort to take over.
I'll make my stance clear:
I back Ah Qiang for the job.
You asked to meet me
because of Liang Zhiqiang.
I just wanted to talk with you
about your story.
He's told me some of it.
I know you two grew up together.
When we were kids, my mom used to make fish soup,
and every kid in the village would fight over it.
Everyone wanted more.
But him,
he would save all the fish in his bowl for me.
He's just that kind of person,
someone who saves the best for others.
You...
regret it.
You're the one who abandoned him first.
What happened back then,
I had no choice either.
But let the past be the past.
Danni,
you know what?
You and Liang Zhiqiang walk different paths.
People aren't just black or white.
But Liang Zhiqiang
was born to walk this path.
So he's born to take the knife for others,
to take the fall for others?
Yes.
He made mistakes,
but he also paid the price
for the mistakes he made.
And now?
You're all doing fine.
But for over twenty years,
all the blame,
all the grievances, he bore them alone.
Did anyone ever care about him?
Even just one word?
Why should he leave the best for others?
I really wish
he'd love himself a little more.
For twenty years,
everyone has wanted to know
what really happened that day.
But for the sake of his brothers, he said nothing.
And yet, he told you all of this.
Honestly, I truly hope
he can find his own happiness.
But Danni,
being with Liang Zhiqiang isn't easy.
Are you prepared for that?
Being with Liang Zhiqiang
is a choice I made after much thought.
Thank you for reaching out to me.
You've both come a long way on this path.
Liang Zhiqiang turned back.
I believe you can too.
The police have never,
and will never tolerate any criminal syndicates.
You think this chump change is enough?
So it really was him.
But Ah Gill took the crucial evidence,
the USB drive.
Once we get that evidence,
we can take down the entire Heyisheng Group.
Ah Fei,
just pull off this one job,
and you can graduate.
Fei!
Be careful!
Zihao, you're awake.
Why'd you sleep in so late?
We're having barbecue today.
Take a look.
It smells amazing.
Zihao!
Zihao, what's wrong?
Don't touch me!
Zihao, tell Mom, quickly!
What's wrong, Zihao?
Don't touch me!
Don't scare me, Zihao!
What's wrong with him?
Don't touch me!
Are you okay?
Zihao!
Zihao, don't scare Mom!